[Music]
this is a National
Emergency Detonator
[Music]
charged we're in the race against the
Nazis
and I know what it
means if the Nazis have a
bomb we have a 12mon head start 18 how
could you possibly know
that we've got one
hope all America's industrial might and
scientific innovation connected
here secret
laboratory keep everyone there until
it's done
let's go recruit some
scientists build a town build it fast we
don't let scientist bring their families
will'll never get the
best why would we go to the middle of
nowhere for who knows how
long why why how about because this is
the most important thing that ever
happened in the history of the
world you're the great improviser but
this
you can't do in your
head are we saying there's a chance that
when we push that button we destroy the
world chances are near
zero near zero what do you want from
Theory alone zero would be
[Music]
nice this is a matter of life and
death but I can perform this
miracle War War II would be over our
boys would come
home that's happening isn't
it the
world will remember this
day our work here will ensure a peace
mankind has never
seen until somebody builds a bigger one
you are the man who gave them the power
to destroy
themselves and the world is not
[Music]
prepared
4 3 Truman needs to know what's next two
what's next one